原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     千只鹤飞过波千鸟  tong大梨  VioletCheng
翻译     AlgerDestiny  克里斯托啊托  五天  不见武汉
校对     屯栗子
时间轴     兜兜兜爹
后期     渔夫
总监     屯栗子
辛普森一家
第31季 第11集
我还能活几天呢
I got few days left!
环保斗士
完蛋了
你好小姐
Hey, little lady.
你笑起来会好看得多
You'd be a lot prettier if you smiled.
什么鬼  你谁啊
What? Who are you?
我是个男人  所以我知道我在说什么
I'm a man. So I know what I'm talking about.
笑一笑  你会变得很受欢迎
Smile and you'll be a lot more popular.
你认真的吗  你知道我会记一辈子吧
Are you serious? You know I'll remember this forever, right?
所以才有心理治疗嘛
Well, that's what therapy's for.
他还跟我说我要是不笑就不好看
And he told me I wouldn't be pretty unless I smiled.
亲爱的  你可美了
Sweetie, you are very pretty.
感谢手机上的青春预测软件
And thanks to the puberty app on my phone,
我们可以看到未来你会变成什么样子
we can see what lies ahead.
青年时期预测
无社交生活
慢着  这不可能
Wait. This can't be real.
我已经带过牙箍了
I already had braces.
恐怕你得再矫正一次了
Oh. Well, I-I'm afraid you have to get them again.
我们找的那个整形牙医
The man we thought was your orthodontist
其实是个冒牌的
was actually a rogue periodontist.
冒牌的整形牙医
Rogue periodontist.
这个家什么地方都要省钱
This family cheaps out on everything.
侯默带我去见"精神病学家"
Homer took me to a "Psychiatrist."
三个疗程之后  我发现是个戴着眼镜的山羊
After three sessions, I figured out it was a goat with glasses.
再也不去了
Never went back.
牙箍  又戴
Braces? Again?
这个家里怎么就我要牙箍
Why am I the only one in this family who needs braces?
别得意  臭小子
Don't look so smug, boy.
咱们在你身上试试这个软件
Let's try this app on you.
你好  阿伦·艾克哈特
Hello, Aaron Eckhart.
预测软件牛逼
Whoa-ho! Puberty!
看看后来怎样
Let's see what comes next.
安息吧
巴仔·辛普森
死于17岁
太酷了
Cool.
侯默快看  我们今天刚收到的
Homie, look. We got this in the mail today.
这是什么
Aw, what is it?
献给侯默和马姬·辛普森
我是不是又喝醉了在易趣网上乱买
Did I get drunk and buy useless stuff on eBay again?
折扣糖果
毛里·波维奇父权剧集
咱再买点
Let's get more.
你好辛普森
Hello, Simpsons.
是我  阿提·齐夫
It's me, Artie Ziff,
活生生提前录好的音
in prerecorded form.
所以你没法跟我说话
So you can't talk to me.
没法说话
I can't?
不  没法说话
No, you can't.
暂停大笑
Pause for laughs.
谢谢你
And thank you.
阿提·齐夫  不就是那个有钱人
Artie Ziff? Isn't that the rich guy
本来可以做我们爸爸
who could have been our dad?
我是你妈妈唯一处过的对象
I am the only man your mother has ever been with,
她一点儿不后悔
and she doesn't have a single regret.
-这个嘛  -你别说话  马姬
- Well... - You stay out of this, Marge!
大新闻  我要结婚了  你们被邀请了
Great news: I'm geg married, and you're invited!
你问为什么我会结婚
Why, you ask, am I getting married?
我找到我的灵魂伴侣啦  嫉妒不
I've found my s-o-u-l mate! Jealous?
参加
不参加
四月十二号  土豪婚礼
April 12th, very rich man's wedding.
只请会后悔的人
Regrets only.
吃鸡还是吃鱼
Chicken or fish.
还是吃素
Or vegan.
废柴
再见
Bye!
邮件里还有什么
So, what else is in the mail?
我们收到了劳氏的传单
We got a flyer from Lowe's!
两厘米厚的胶合板
Three-quarter plywood.
20块钱一块
$20 a sheet!
我要去了
I'm a-comin'!
我没有车
Oh, I don't have a car.
你不会真的想去吧
You're not really thinking of going, are you?
那个混蛋想让我们分开
That jerk kept trying to break us up.
现在  我感受到了矛盾
Now, I am sensing conflicted feelings.
如果你来  我保证你会度过一段完美的时光
If you come, I promise you a wonderful time.
香槟  鱼子酱
Champagne, caviar,
油炸冰雕  一个一直在猜你体重的男人
deep-fried ice sculptures, a guy who guesses your weight,
永远都猜得很低
who always guesses low!
接受
谢谢
Thank you.
现在开始庆祝  请出图派克·夏库尔
And now to celebrate, here's Tupac Shakur!
*不要迟到*
*Don't be tardy*
*我哥们阿提要开派对了*
*My boy Artie is throwing a party*
*派对一定最最时尚*
*This wedding's gonna be fly*
*你们为什么就是不让我死呢*
*Why won't you people let me die?*
这东西怎么关掉
How do you turn this off?
阿提的表演不能关闭
There's no off to the Artie show.
-我来决定什么时候...  -求你放了我吧
- I decide when... - Please set me free.
在这里
Oh, here it is.
关闭
上帝保佑你
God bless you.
科兹卢矫正
科兹卢医生
现在每一颗都完美了  漱口吧
Now everyone's favorite: rinse and spit.
做好了  上面的牙套
And I'm done... with the top braces.
下周把下面的套好
We'll put booms in next week.
之后  就要戴一辈子牙套了
And after that, just a lifetime of wearing retainers.
他们基本上是隐形的
Well, they're practically invisible.
我闭不上嘴了
I can't close my mouth.
牙套的边缘挡住了你的嘴唇
The brackets are holding up your lips at the edges.
会适应的  重要的事情是  你开心了
They'll adjust. The main thing is you're happy.
我不开心
I'm not happy.
吸点笑气
Have a little nitrous.
他们真应该吊销你的执照
Oh, they should revoke your license. Ha!
再来点
More, please.
-这就够了  -不  不够
- That's enough. - No, it's not!
好了快给我吧
Yeah, give me that.
我还以为你叫科兹卢
I thought your name is "Kidzrule."
科兹卢拉维奇的简称
Shortened from "Kidzrulovitch,"
罗马尼亚语的杀光所有小孩
which is Romanian for "Kill all the children."
单身派对  距离婚礼两天
这部电梯最多能载32个人
That elevator has the capacity for 32 people!
上周运了一只犀牛上来
We brought a rhino up here last week.
请选龙虾
请选小牛犊
请选超级碗戒指
我的头好痛
My headaches are so bad.
嫉妒吗
Jealous?
着陆
Feet.
你是万里挑一的
You're one in a million.
字面意思上的  别从房顶上掉下去
Literally. Don't fall off the roof.
侯默·辛普森
Homer Simpson!
赢得了我的马姬芳心的男人
The man who bet me to planet Marge.
对于一个亿万富翁来说  你做得挺好的了
You've done all right for a billionaire.
我又不是钱做的
Hey, I'm not made of money.
但是  其实我是
Although, actually I am.
假释之后
After my parole,
我靠着卖做成纸币的壁炉木柴发了家
I got rich selling fireplace logs that look like cash,
它叫烧钱
i.E., Money to Burn.
烧钱
这是最棒的
That is the greatest.
那上面写着"烧钱"
It says "Money to Burn."
看起来就像是在烧钱一样
It looks like you're burning money!
是啊  就是这个意思
Yes, that's the idea.
不  不  不
No, no, no.
太搞笑了  你没明白吗
It's so funny. Don't you get it?
我当然明白  是我想到的
Of course I get it. I thought of it.
不  不  不  听着  上面写着"花不完的钱"
No, no, no. Listen, it says "Money to Burn",
但其实是...
but it's actually...
我知道  我知道  跟别人说去吧
I know! I know! Talk to someone else.
老兄  你是新闻界的  跟我直说吧
Hey, pal, you're a news guy. Give it to me straight.
这场婚礼真实可信吗
Is this wedding on the level?
独家新闻  这是合法的
Here's the scoop. It's legit!
其他地方的新闻记者希望能勾搭上筹办者
In other news, local newsman hopes to score with caterer.
插播消息  她知道我是已婚人士
This just in: she knows I'm married.
十一点即将播出  什么都没有
Coming up at 11:00: nothing.
侯默  这是个单身派对
Now, Homer, as this is a bachelor party,
我想给你看点东西
I want to show you something.
但别跟妻子们说
But, uh, no word to the wives.
话说你是怎么认识你妻子的
How did you meet your wife, by the way?
很普通  男孩遇上女孩  女孩遇上银行账户
Usual: boy meets girl, girl meets bank account.
现在闭上眼睛
Now, shut your eyes.
你从未见过如此诱人的胴体
You've never seen a body this enticing.
正如我所想
Exactly what I imagined!
食物昏迷  他会没事的
Food coma. He'll be fine.
饱餐一顿后感到昏昏欲睡
你好  女朋友
Hey, girlfriend!
谁  我吗
Uh, who, me?
丽莎  你去做了眉毛脱毛吗
Lisa, did you get your eyebrows waxed?
你看起来真棒
You look amazing!
我没有眉毛
I don't have eyebrows.
看看我这对毛毛虫
Well, check out these twin caterpillars.
怎么回事
What's going on?
她的笑容让我感到饱足
Her smile makes me feel full,
就像我昨晚真的吃了晚饭一样
like I actually ate dinner last night.
如果你从不吃饭  你怎么还这么胖
If you never eat, how come you're so fat?
美国人可以胖并贫穷着
Americans can be fat and poor.
正是这一点让我们如此强大
That's what makes us so great.
《夏洛的网》
就这样  在救了威尔伯后
And so, after saving Wilbur,
夏洛爬着爬着  死去了
Charlotte crawled off to die,
就像秋天时所有谷仓里的蜘蛛一样
as all barn spiders do in the fall.
很精彩  丽莎
Bravo, Lisa.
给我们这节课画上了愉快的句号
What a positive note on which to end the class.
愉快  愉快吗
Positive? Positive?
夏洛在地球上最悲伤的地方独自死去了
Charlotte died alone at the saddest place on Earth,
在一个空荡荡的露天游乐场中
an empty fairground.
你的微笑让独自死去变得有趣了
Well, your smiling face made dying alone fun.
相信我  我就是这么打算的
And believe me, that's where I'm headed.
所以只要我在微笑
So as long as I'm smiling,
从我口中说出什么样的话都不重要吗
it doesn't matter what comes out of my mouth?
从鼻子中也是
Or your nose.
我不再需要这些了
I don't need these anymore.
舍曲林[抗抑郁药物]
这个可以加到威利的炖菜里
This'll go good in Willie's stew.
人们真的这么肤浅吗
Can it really be that people are this shallow?
丽莎  丽莎  丽莎
Lisa! Lisa! Lisa!
而且我有肤浅到乐在其中吗
And am I shallow enough to enjoy this?
的确如此
I am!
我太开心了  我可以唱歌
I'm so happy, I could sing!
*你好  世界*
*Hello, world!*
撑得我好疼
That really hurts with the braces.
-选一个吧  -这是什么
- Take your pick. - What is it?
不知道  上面写的是西班牙语
No idea. The labels are in Spanish.
春田小学
-你好  美女  -你好  巴仔
- Hey, gorgeous. - Hey, Bart.
丽莎  恶心死了  我不知道是你
Lisa? Oh, yuck! I didn't know that was you.
微笑让人们完全改变了对我的看法
It's the smile. It's totally changed how people see me.
我只是想让你知道  你一直都让我恶心
Well, I just want you to know, you'll always be gross to me.
谢天谢地  我一直有个疑问
Oh, thank God. I was having doubts,
想弄清楚这是不是性别歧视
trying to figure out if this is sexist.
谢天谢地我找到了这个
And then I found this.
不要给学生看也不要扔掉
把它放在图书馆的低架子上
女性职场指南
自从避孕药发明之后
It seems like ever since the pill,
职场里好像到处都是单身女性
the workplace has been full of single women.
给你咖啡  吉姆
Here's your coffee, Jim.
多糖  就像你喜欢的一样
Extra sugar, just how you like it.
我要去离婚了
Hmm. Remind me to get a divorce.
但是一些女性在"融合"的过程中有困难
But some women are having trouble "Fitting in."
我一直都搞不明白  吉姆
Well, I can't figure it out, Jim.
我准备了一场大型的演讲
I was all prepared for a big presentation,
就像修女站在舞厅里
but it went over like a nun at a go-go bar.
你有一件事没有准备好
Well, there's one thing you didn't prepare,
就是你的脸
and that's your face.
但是我都用了玫琳凯的化妆品
But I'm wearing a pound of Mary Kay.
让我接触你的身体告诉你问题所在
Let me touch your body and show you the problem.
没问题
No need to ask.
在你的脸上
You've got a secret weapon
藏着一个秘密武器
sitting in the middle of your face.
你现在肯定获得提拔了
Now you're sure to get that promotion.
真的吗
Really?
不会
No.
你不知道我为什么很讨厌这件事吗
Ugh! Don't you see why I hate this?
因为你厌恶一切
'Cause you hate everything?
因为这让那个讨厌的老家伙听起来很正确
Because it makes that jerky old guy right!
我受到欢迎就是因为我会微笑
I am more popular ‭because I'm smiling.
就是这样
Told ya!
没有一张照片是阿蒂的
Wow. Not a single picture of Artie.
欢迎来到齐夫的婚礼
也许他已经成熟了
Maybe he has matured.
对自己很满意
来到这里感觉就像结束了人生的一个阶段
Well, I guess being here sort of ends a chapter in life.
这值得庆祝
So, lehayim.
好奇怪
That's odd.
新娘的家人都没来
Not one person from the bride's family.
打扰一下  我们需要人去陪新娘走红毯
Excuse me. We need someone walk with bride down the aisle.
你可以吗
Could you?
你先告诉我这个过道有多长
First, tell me one thing: how long is the aisle?
大约二十英尺
About 20 feet.
好吧  我去
All right, I'll do it.
但是我要双份蛋糕
But double cake.
她们这么快就长大了
They grow up so fast.
我知道这一天总会来的
I knew this day would come.
你永远是我的小宝贝
You'll always be my little girl. Mm.
如果他敢伤害我的孩子  我会杀了他
If he hurts my baby, I'll kill him.
你也入戏太深了吧
Oh, for crying out loud.
朋友们  家人们
Friends, family,
非常高兴的告诉大家
I take great delight in informing you
新郎和新娘已经写下了他们的誓言
that the bride and groom have written their own vows.
跟着剧本走  伙计们
Stick to the script, amateurs!
我的天
Oh my god!
这太奇怪了
This is too weird.
阿蒂  你是我见过最好的爱人
Artie, you're the greatest lover ever,
当我们滚床单的时候感觉非常棒
when we made sex is so-so good.
我受不了了
I can't take this anymore.
我们快离开这里
We're getting out of here.
没错  这里太诡异了
Yeah. This is really creepy.
连犀牛都走了
Even the rhino's leaving.
你现在可以亲吻新娘了
You may now kiss the bride!
这幅画画的是婚礼上的我们
And this is a picture of us at our wedding.
你特别开心
You're so happy.
这是我们在度蜜月
And here's us on our honey moon.
在俄亥俄两天  在密歇根两天  然后
Two days in Ohio, and two days in Michigan, and boo-yah!
永耐驰
新婚燕尔
再去安大略感受一些异国风情
To Ontario for some international flavor!
我不开心
I'm not happy.
我还画了一张你在密歇根说这句话的画呢
I have a drawing of you saying that in Michigan.
这个笑容很有问题
This smile is so wrong.
没有什么值得开心的事
There's nothing to be happy about.
世界一团糟  学校也是
The world's a mess, and so is this school.
可回收
你看  这有多难吗
I mean, how hard is this?
一个开心的姑娘把那个东西放进了洞里
A happy girl put the thing in the hole.
等等  我可以用我的新能力去改变这些
Wait a minute, I could use my new power to change these things.
用它造福一方
Use it for good!
春田小学禅意花园
石棉
芦笋
毫无疑问
Indubitably.
说得好  说得好
Hear, hear! Hear, hear!
我可以让这些成为现实
I can make it happen.
快点啊
Hurry!
选丽莎当学生会主席
快来踢我
快去给丽莎投票
丽莎
忠实  诚信  学识渊博  笑容迷人
你们这些假惺惺的人
You posers.
在它流行起来之前我就支持丽莎了
I was for Lisa before it was cool.
你从没喜欢过丽莎
You never liked Lisa.
什么  这你不能忘了吧
What? You got to remember that.
这是我最大的特点啊
That's my one thing!
不  你的特点是挨打之后会哭
No. Your thing is crying you're punched.
那就试试吧
Prove it.
你把它搞得都不好玩了
Aw, you're taking all the fun out of it.
民调结果出来了  你的结果不错
The polls are in, and you're doing great.
你抓住了不喜欢苗浩斯的姑娘们的心
You're picking up the key group: girls who don't like Milhouse.
你在秋千摇摆选民那里反响不错
You're big with swing voters,
但跷跷板浮动选民那边可能时上时下
but the teeter-totters could go either way.
滑梯上的那些呢
What about the kids on the slide?
他们有上有下的
Eh, they're up and down,
但攀爬架上那边在直线攀升
but the kids on the monkey bars are climbing.
我知道的就这些
That's all I got.
和所有只剩一周的选举一样
Like every election with one week to go,
我们已经把它拿下了
this is in the bag.
别这么早下定论
Don't be so sure.
我的对手很强
I'm up against a tough opponent:
达不溜·斯帕科勒
Dubya Spuckler.
佬自要参选
你看看他做的这个负面广告
Look at this negative ad he did.
丽莎·辛普森说"鞋作"的"鞋"读三声
Lisa Simpson says "Writin'" ends with a "G"
还说"酸术"的"酸"读四声
and "'rithmetic" starts with a "A."
但你知道我要说什么吗
You know what I say?
别担心  保持微笑就好
Don't worry. You just keep smiling.
我预约了明天去看牙医
Well, I do have an orthodontist appointment tomorrow
去做个微调
for a tune-up.
胜券在握  主席女士
In the bag, Madam President.
停  先别那么肯定
Bup, don't be so sure.
你看  我画了一张你的就职典礼
Hey, I drew a picture of your inauguration.
我觉得这是我最快乐的时候了
I don't think I've ever looked more radiant.
科兹卢矫正
好了孩子  你下牙的牙套戴好了
Okay, kid. Your bottom braces are on.
我的微笑呢
What happened to my smile?
不不不  坏大事了
No, no, no, this is terrible.
我表里如一了
I look like I actually feel.
六个月后  你会有一口好牙
In six months, you'll have perfect teeth.
六个月  我现在就得笑
Six months? I have to smile now.
不  我能对抗它
No, I can power through this.
拉尔夫的牙齿保持器丢垃圾桶了
Uh, Ralph lost his retainer in the trash.
有什么办法吗
What can we, uh, do here?
一副五百
New ones a $500.
所以秘密任务是什么  警长
Uh, so just what is this secret mission, Chief?
正前方死亡垃圾岛
这么说吧  你们被雇用了
Well, let's just say you're on retainer.
-我想想  拿这个  -你别拿了
-Let's see. I'll take this. -Aw, stop that.
马姬  这迷你吧咱掏过钱的
Aw, come on, Marge. This minibar is paid for.
你知道这三角巧克力的市价吗
Do you know the street value of this Toblerone?
侯默  别拿了行吗
Homer, stop it.
我总不由自主想起那可怜的女人
I can't help thinking about that poor woman.
阿蒂娶她只因为她长得像我
Artie only married her because she looks like me.
非常像
I mean, a lot like me.
没错  我们得去找她  告诉她
You're right. We have to find her and tell her.
但首先  我想对这床干点
But, first, there's something naughty
淘气的事
I want to do with this bed.
我们来这合适吗
Are you sure we should be here?
严格地说  今天是人家的蜜月
This is technically his honeymoon.
阿蒂
Artie?
我正处在人生最低谷
I'm at the lowest point of my life!
但请进吧
But come on in.
同为女人  我想跟你妻子坦白
As a woman, I just want to tell your wife
发生了的事
what's really going on here.
太好了
Sure, why not?
冲她脸说
Say it to her face!
现在你知道我的秘密了
Now you know my secret.
我花费多年时间企图为自己做一个
I've spent years trying to build the perfect copy
完美唯一的女人  就是你  马姬
of the only woman for me: you, Marge.
但她们或多或少都有缺陷
But they were all inferior in somy.
她缺善良
This one lacks kindness.
她想杀我
This one keeps trying to kill me.
她的头是烤面包机
This one's head is a toaster!
而且连百吉饼都塞不下
And the slots aren't even big enough for a bagel!
你为什么要娶一台机器
Why would you marry a machine?
我不想
I didn't.
我只是走投无路
It was one last trick.
我认为你看到咱俩在一起有多配时
I thought when you saw how perfect we look together,
你会意识到我们天生一对
you would realize that we were meant to be.
像诗里说的那样  我就是个愚蠢的笨蛋
I am, as the poet once said, a dumb schmuck.
-阿蒂  -在
- Artie. - Yes?
你不傻  你很聪明
You're not dumb. You're smart.
我认为这些疯狂实验里
And I think this crazy project
有你独特的闪光处
actually had some brilliance in it.
想想实验用对了路子会怎么样
Imagine if you use that noodle for good.
哇
Wow. Wow.
只有你能读懂我像牡蛎里珍珠般的珍贵
Only you could find a pearl in the flabby oyster that is me.
我会变成更好的人
I will become a better human being.
真不错
Terrific.
然后你就会爱我吗
And then you'll love me?
当然不会
No.
好吧  我终于要放弃了
Well, then, I finally give up.
我放弃了吗
Or do I?
他妈的
Aw, damn it.
阿蒂  你和你的蓝色马姬小队
Artie, you and your blue crew of Margekateers
阿蒂·齐夫孤儿院
做了这么多善事
have done so many good deeds.
接下来有何计划
What's next?
我会娶她们其中一个
I'm gonna make one of them my bride.
嘿  我没给你们装翅膀啊
Hey, I didn't give you wings.
出路要靠自己找
Life finds a way!
学生会竞选辩论
败者留校查看
同学们  安静下来
Uh, let's quiet down, please.
这场辩论早点结束
The sooner we can get this debate over,
老师们就能早点吃上冰淇淋
the sooner the teachers can get ice cream.
西摩不能吃  他有胃病
None for Seymour. He gets gassy.
是的  我知道
Yeah I-I know.
下面有请特邀辩论主持人
And now we have a very special moderator,
玛丽·贝莉州长
Governor Mary Bailey.
第一位候选人是达不溜·斯帕科勒
Our first candidate is Dubya Spuckler.
达不溜  达不溜
Dubya! Dubya!
这是你哥哥
That's your brother.
他更愿意被称为"他们"
He prefers the pronoun "They,"
因为在我的子宫里他吃掉了自己的双胞胎兄弟
on account of the twin he absorbed in my belly.
另一位候选人因病只能用视频通话的方式参加
Our other candidate is ill, so she'll be Skyping in.
丽莎·辛普森
Lisa Simpson.
丽莎  很遗憾你病了  你有什么症状
Lisa, I'm sorry, what do you have?
我有的是对学校的一腔热血
What I have is an agenda for this school
和一颗勇往直前的心
an agenda that looks forward.
我是个结果导向的人  而我的对手
I can deliver results, while my opponent
连结果两个字都不会写
can't even spell "Results."
我当然会
Yes, I can. R-E squiggly letter,
姐姐的"姐"
buet letter, tall man,
还有苹果树的"果"
little plus sign, squiggly letter.
"姐果"
"Results."
根本就不对
That's not how you spell "Results."
丽莎听起来根本没生病
Lisa doesn't sound sick at all.
你说你以前做过这个
You said you've done this before.
我想表现的爷们一点才那么说的
It was my machismo talking.
丽莎在用鬼脸软件
Lisa's using a funny-face app.
听着  我试图愚弄大家  是我做错了
Listen, I tried to fool you, and that was wrong.
令人作呕
This is an abomination!
你来学校辩论会干嘛
What are you doing at a school debate?
我的私生子是这里的学生
My illegitimate son goes here.
真丢人
Oh, the shame.
我还有很多好想法
I still have good ideas.
在我听来全是废话
All I hear is "Nag, nag, nag."
达不溜  达不溜
Dubya! Dubya!
全完了
Oh, boy.
我不想承认大家喜欢我
I didn't want to believe my popularity was
是因为我的笑容
based on my stupid smile.
但事实如此
Oh, but it was.
你还是个孩子  而且时代在改变
You're just a kid, and things are changing.
也许未来社会评价女人的标准
In the future, women will be judged
不再是根据容貌  而是根据内在
by what they say, not how they look.
也许吧  但这个未来真的很远
Maybe, but the future is a really long way away.
告诉过你应该多笑一笑的
Told you you should smile more.
未来已经到来了
The future is now!
请举杯  我终于将你们改造完美了
A toast. I have finally perfected you.
你们的容貌都和马姬一样  而且永远不会离开
You all look just like Marge, and you will never leave.
有哪个幸运女孩想和阿提一起派对
Now, which of you lucky girls wants to party with Arty?
我正处于省电模式
I am in power save mode.
好吧  那你们俩呢
Oh, fine. What about you two?
省电模式
Power save.
剩余电量不足
One percent battery.
我只是不喜欢你罢了
I just don't like you.
这算间接接吻
Oh! That counts as a kiss.